// Answer text must be under 25 characters otherwise they'll be truncated
// Answer value but be the lowercase LETTER of the correct answer (a, b, c, or d)
// All games must be 10 questions - do not delete any!

// JK Rowling Ruined My Childhood

module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What is the media criticsm term for when established elements in a fictional work are adjusted, ignored, or contradicted by a later published work which breaks continuity in the earlier work?', 
      a: 'irony', 
      b: 'poststructuralism',
      c: 'Retcon',
      d: 'intentional fallacy',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'What platform does Rowling commonly use to retcon her stories?', 
      a: 'Twitter', 
      b: 'Her Facebook Page',
      c: 'Owls',
      d: 'MuggleNet',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
        question: 'What character did Rowling state in a 2007 press conference was gay all along?', 
        a: 'Luna Lovegood', 
        b: 'Albus Dubmledore',
        c: 'Newt Scamander',
        d: 'Kreacher',
        answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What did Rowling later state the werewolves symbolized?', 
      a: 'American Evangelicals', 
      b: 'German Nazis',
      c: 'HIV victims',
      d: 'Russian Pogroms',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'The literary theory stating that a work belongs only to its fans after itâ€™s written is called:', 
      a: 'Reader Rennaissance', 
      b: 'Authorial Intent',
      c: 'Collective Unconscious',
      d: 'Death of the Author',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'What reason did director David Yates give for not portraying Dumbeldore as gay in Fantastic Beats: the Crimes of Grindlewald?', 
      a: 'Objection from the studio', 
      b: '\"Fans already know\"',
      c: 'Outrage from conservative fans',
      d: 'He wasn\'t aware',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Ironically, what fan community did Rowling publicly endorse in 2004?', 
      a: 'Fan fics', 
      b: 'Cosplay',
      c: 'Unlicensed merchandise',
      d: 'Song parodies',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the media criticism term for hinting that a character is gay without confirming that?', 
      a: 'Gay coding', 
      b: 'Straightsplaining',
      c: 'Essentialism',
      d: 'Queerbaiting',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following is NOT a retcon Rowling has stated of her characters?', 
      a: 'Nagini was a Korean woman', 
      b: 'Hermione was black all along',
      c: 'Hagrid did not have a patronus',
      d: 'Sirius was gay',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of these authors took time to re-write earlier works when they learned of negative impacts on children?', 
      a: 'JRR Tolkein', 
      b: 'Dr. Suess',
      c: 'Richard Scarry',
      d: 'Martin Hanford',
      answer: 'c'
    }
  ]
};